<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>

	<string id="zone_mine_radar_section_name">
		<text>Radar</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="zone_mine_darkness_section_name">
		<text>Darkness</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="zone_mine_flash_section_name">
		<text>Flash</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="zone_mine_ghost_section_name">
		<text>Ghost</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="zone_mine_gold_section_name">
		<text>Liquid Gold</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="zone_mine_green_dragon_section_name">
		<text>Green Dragon</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="zone_mine_mefistotel_section_name">
		<text>Mephistopheles</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="zone_mine_net_section_name">
		<text>Net</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="zone_mine_point_section_name">
		<text>Ball Lightning</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="zone_mine_sphere_section_name">
		<text>Rebounder</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_radar">
		<text>Radar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_radar_text">
		<text>
			• Name: %c[d_cyan]Radar%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Type: %c[d_orange]Psionic
			\n \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]
			\nA localized breach in the Noosphere. It emits a weak psionic aura, severely harming the mental health of anyone staying within its vicinity, by scrambling their brain wave frequencies. Unlike regular psi-fields, stalkers tend to avoid these anomalies entirely, since their influence bypasses any conventional means of psionic protection, affecting the victim's mind directly. 
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_darkness">
		<text>Darkness</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_darkness_text">
		<text>
			• Name: %c[d_cyan]Darkness%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Type: %c[d_orange]Psionic
			\n \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]
			\nA terrifying and deadly anomalous formation of unknown origin, affecting the mind of any sentient being within its vicinity. It resembles a cluster of moving shadows. There are rumours that the anomaly also acts as a shelter for poltergeists. One of the most dangerous anomalies ever recorded in the Zone.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_flash">
		<text>Flash</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_flash_text">
		<text>
			• Name: %c[d_cyan]Flash%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Type: %c[d_orange]Temporal
			\n \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]
			\nA rift in the space-time continuum. Any creature caught in these anomalies, experiences a rapid time-travel of unknown temporal extent. Despite their seemingly dangerous nature, some stalkers cleverly use these rifts for their own purposes, such as escaping from pursuit or waiting for the best moment to snatch an artefact. 
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_ghost">
		<text>Ghost</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_ghost_text">
		<text>
			• Name: %c[d_cyan]Ghost%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Type: %c[d_orange]Electrical/Chemical
			\n \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]
			\nA spherical, electro-chemical anomaly. Its most distinctive feature is that it moves along a fixed path within a certain area, as if aware of its surroundings and in search for prey. This behavioural pattern gave rise to many metaphysical theories, suggesting that this anomaly may actually be a sentient manifestation, rather than a natural abnormality. 
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_gold">
		<text>Liquid Gold</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_gold_text">
		<text>
			• Name: %c[d_cyan]Liquid Gold%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Type: %c[d_orange]Chemical
			\n \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]
			\nConsidered as a twin sister of the "Fruit Punch" anomaly, "Liquid Gold" emits a cloud of orange/gold toxic chemical substance. This substance raises the victim's body temperature to levels beyond feverish, and at an extremely fast rate, triggering a wide range of symptoms depending on the anomaly's potency: from severe dehydration, to an instant death caused by the victim's blood reaching its boiling point.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_green_dragon">
		<text>Green Dragon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_green_dragon_text">
		<text>
			• Name: %c[d_cyan]Green Dragon%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Type: %c[d_orange]Chemical
			\n \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]
			\nAn anomalous cloud of unknown chemical composition. This cloud - classified as poisonous - adversely affects the biological functions of any trapped organism, greatly hindering their motor skills. Physical actions involving fast movement, like running or jumping, are very hard to perform within its vicinity.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_mefistotel">
		<text>Mephistopheles</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_mefistotel_text">
		<text>
			• Name: %c[d_cyan]Mephistopheles%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Type: %c[d_orange]Electrical/Chemical
			\n \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]
			\nTaking its name after the trickster demon of medieval folklore, this strange flower-like formation emits an eerie sound when any living organism approaches it. Victims entering its active radius, are instantly drawn to its center and shredded into pieces. A beautiful, yet extremely dangerous anomaly.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_net">
		<text>Net</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_net_text">
		<text>
			• Name: %c[d_cyan]Net%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Type: %c[d_orange]Gravitational/Electrical
			\n \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]
			\nThis formation is a stream of charged particles, further accelerated by gravitational forces. Any object within the anomaly's effective radius, gets rapidly enveloped by these particles, in a similar fashion to that of a net, hence its namesake. 
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_point">
		<text>Ball Lightning</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_point_text">
		<text>
			• Name: %c[d_cyan]Ball Lightning%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Type: %c[d_orange]Electrical
			\n \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]
			\nAn anomaly of electrical nature, reminiscent of the famous and yet unexplained natural phenomenon. It has an unconfirmed interaction with electrical objects, especially with batteries and capacitors, allegedly charging them with electric energy. Nevertheless, unless heavily protected, it is strongly advised not to approach the anomaly.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_sphere">
		<text>Rebounder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_sphere_text">
		<text>
			• Name: %c[d_cyan]Rebounder%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n• Type: %c[d_orange]Gravitational
			\n \n%c[pda_green]Information%c[ui_gray_1]
			\nThis gravitational anomaly is a dense concentration of multiple force waves, forming some kind of disc perpendicular to the ground. The disc can act as an unorthodox shield or cover, that repels or reduces the speed of fast moving objects, such as bullets or other projectiles. Some more experienced stalkers have been witnessed using the "Rebounder" to their advantage during combat situations.
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>